My condolences.
We are all Mr. Mu's students.
His passing was very sudden.
We came to pay our last respects.
All the students are here.
Everyone who should be here has come.
That's very thoughtful.
Thank you.
My condolences.
She knew her husband was like this,
but she doesn't mind at all.
She really minds.
From the beginning until now,
she hasn't looked at the portrait once.
It's subconscious resistance.
Then why is she so calm?
What else?
Should she make a huge scene
and let the whole world know her husband is a rapist?
This funeral is the last bit of dignity she can give Mu Weijie.
Look.
Why are those students all young girls?
You don't know?
I heard Mr. Mu was quite a player.
died on a little girl.
I don't know who.
Really.
The bureau's confidentiality work is not in place.
Yes.
Go find out
where the news leaked.
Yes, sir.
Do you know her?
No.
Then you won't get anything out of her.
From a psychological perspective,
the human brain's amygdala
will quickly activate an alert response to strangers.
Mr. Cheng.
I may not know psychology,
but you don't understand older women.
Sisters!
What kind of reaction is that?
Such a sweet-talking girl.
I'm old enough to be your aunt, not your sister.
I told you.
Everyone in our bureau
is a talent.
You're so amazing, sister.
How do you know everything?
We neighbors are very well-informed.
Then am I considered a talent?
Just watch.
Thank you, sisters.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
I'll get going now. Bye.
So? Did you find out anything?
Slow down.
I'm exhausted.
Their information is incomplete.
However,
someone seems to be deliberately spreading rumors about Mu Weijie's death.
Organized and premeditated.
Looks like someone can't sit still anymore.
They definitely can't.
Lin Rongrong.
Can I talk to her alone for a moment?
Xiaoyue.
Don't be afraid.
Go ahead and talk.
I'll wait for you outside.
Let's go take a look.
Don't worry.
Jiang Yifei knows her limits.
Hello, officers.
How much?
Just name a price.
I want you to admit
that it was consensual with my husband.
Miss Jiang, what are you talking about?
I...
I was...
raped.
I don't care.
And I don't have time to bargain with you.
Besides,
didn't you come here today
just to ask me for money?
That's not true.
Miss Jiang,
you misunderstood.
I didn't come for money.
Then what do you want?
You two are very close.
We grew up together.
She's my best friend.
By the way,
Officer Zhuang.
Will Allen
be okay?
The case is still under investigation.
I can't tell you the result yet.
I'll leave it to you then.
You must find out the truth for Mr. Mu
so he can rest in peace.
Don't worry.
If he hasn't broken the law,
he will be fine.
If he has,
none of them will get away.
Yes.
Heaven will punish the wicked.
Lin Rongrong.
You had this all figured out.
I put a lot of effort
into making Mu Weijie a famous painter.
If his reputation is ruined now,
his unsold paintings won't sell.
Right?
You win.
But there is a limit to how much more I can pay.
Don't push it.
I'll say it again.
I don't want money.
I won't compromise no matter how much you pay me.
He raped me.
Enough.
Stop acting like a saint.
The amount is negotiable.
Besides, if I ruin your reputation,
you'll just be a homewrecker.
When that happens,
you still won't get any money.
I suggest you be realistic.
After all, you already slept together.
You're despicable.
Rongrong!
Lin Rongrong!
Rongrong,
I advise you to think things through yourself.
She's the one who killed Mu Weijie.
Miss Jiang,
my condolences.
Wait a minute.
I have another question for you.
Did your husband, Mu Weijie,
have another place to store his paintings?
How did you know
he had another warehouse?
He admired Titian so much,
but in his studio,
there weren't many replicas of Titian's works.
So I concluded
there must be another storage place.
That's right.
He has another warehouse
in the industrial park.
That's where he stayed
before he got famous.
But why are you three
suddenly asking about this?
It's nothing.
We're just asking.
Suit yourselves.
My condolences.
Any results?
You were actually right.
On the student list for this elective course,
believe it or not,
there really are female students learning painting at Mu Weijie's.
I want to know,
is this thing of any use?
It is useful.
Very useful.
It's useful.
Thank you.
We have the evidence.
Bai,
go meet up with Fang.
Keep an eye on Lin Rongrong,
and tell Shao to be ready for the forensic test at any time.
No problem.
Cheng Mo,
we need to go to Mu Weijie's warehouse.
There must be evidence there.
Even if you burn this place down,
you can't burn away all the crimes you've committed.
Right, Xu Qiaoyue?
It really is you.
Officer Zhuang, Officer Cheng,
No, you've misunderstood.
Mr. Mu loved his paintings.
As his student,
I just wanted to burn them for him.
Rather than leaving them here,
it's better to let them accompany him.
You didn't burn them earlier or later,
but chose this exact time.
What a coincidence.
It is a bit of a coincidence.
But what does that prove?
Want some water?
It indeed proves nothing.
But that night,
the one who was supposed to sleep with Mu Weijie was you,
not Lin Rongrong.
Right?
What do you mean?
The day Mr. Mu died,
I wasn't in the studio,
nor was I near it.
How could it be me?
It has nothing to do with me.
Does it really have nothing to do with you?
It really has nothing to do with me.
Officer Zhuang, you're overthinking it.
Lin Rongrong's return to the studio
was just a spur-of-the-moment decision.
But before that,
you and Mu Weijie had already arranged
to meet there.
That's why Mu Weijie took an aphrodisiac in advance.
And Lin Rongrong,
took your place to satisfy his lust.
Good imagination.
But it really has nothing to do with me.
Alan found out long ago
that you were having an affair with Mu Weijie.
Lin Rongrong also said in her testimony,
"Why?"
"Why are we always the ones getting hurt?"
"We."
Aren't you talking about you and her?
Officer Zhuang.
You need evidence to handle a case, right?
Where is your evidence?
We came here to find evidence.
But I didn't expect,
Xu Qiaoyue,
that you couldn't keep your composure.
Do you know what the consequences of your actions mean?
It means
Lin Rongrong will live in the shadows
for the rest of her life.
All because of your selfishness
and revenge.
Doesn't your conscience hurt?
Danaë is imprisoned in the tower.
Zeus turned into a shower of gold and mated with her.
As a tall tower,
the studio is not hidden enough.
It's easy for others to find.
So,
this place
is the real tower.